It turned red!
Thank you!!!
Lehrer was taking pictures the whole time!
I was in the picture the whole time!
Yay!
We are all here in Zhongshan Park!
This is Guam!
This is Guam! There are objects from all over the world!
What a cute picture!
I love it! It's so cute!
So cute!
I want to see pictures of Taiwan!
I want to take pictures!
I like this one!
Okay, let's see Lil' Rua taking a picture.
Oh, that's nice. Did you get it?
Oh, isn't that somehow? The onigiri.
Hey, Miyagi?
Miyagi?
What's that?
Omusubi-kun, you're too picky.
Miyamusubi-kun.
Wow, where is it from?
It's full of animals.
I don't understand.
I don't know.
Oh, wow, it's moving!
It's moving.
I want to ride it.
I'd love to ride it.
Please let me on it. There are a lot of monkeys.
So cute! Monkeys are at home!
This is Matsuyama, Ehime.
I've been there before. Maybe I've been there before.
Mikyan is here.
We know her. Her eyes are tiny.
I finally got a shot.
Third time's the charm.
Zhongshan Park.
I've been calling out to you over and over.
Wow!
That's a real event.
Yeah, I think we may have gotten in on the wrong foot.
Yeah, we might have come in on a weird one.
It's amazing.
Hey, what's that?
What's that?
It looks like a rabbit.
Is that the back?
It says "Hautane Festival" on it.
They're preparing.
Yes, it's ready.
It's ready.
Oh, my God.
Ginseng?
Carrots?
Rabbit festival.
So cute!
Waving carrots around is so cute!
I love it.
Amazing!
Etc... it's the same all over the world, right?
I heard it's the same all over the world.
I wonder if it is.
You know, they have cows and stuff.
China has pigs?
Not boars, but pigs?
Pig? It's a little different.
I mean, the order is the same, but...
What was that?
What was it?
I don't know.
But a rabbit is a rabbit.
A rabbit is a rabbit.
Wow, it's open.
I guess they're still getting ready for the event.
Yeah, it's still open.
I don't know, maybe still preparing.
It won't be open for a little while.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Isn't it amazing? A stage.
It's a stage, I guess. It's so big.
It's nice. I'd love to do a show here.
I'd love to.
Isn't the building tall? All of them.
They're all tall.
Is there anything this tall in Fukuoka? Not really.
Maybe Fukuoka Tower.
That's for sure.
Isn't there music everywhere in Taiwan?
Yes, they do.
Pretty much everywhere.
It's so cute.
A bird.
Oh, wow.
Bugs.
What?
Wow.
Carrots!
Wow, a big carrot here.
So cute.
Lilo, can you stand up? There.
I'll stand.
Jump, jump, jump.
Pooh!
So cute!
She's even leaning over to take a picture of you, Miss Keena.
Yay!
She asked if everyone else wants to take a picture, too.
What should we do, Ms. Keena?
Can everyone join in?
Keena joins in on the fun.
That's nice. They look so cute.
It's adorable.
Thank you very much.
Well, may I join in on the fun?
He's so cute.
Great. I'll take a picture of it.
Nice. Cute.
Cute.
So cute!
There's an official supporter.
We took this picture together.
That's nice.
Let's do it.
Okay, you go first.
He's so cute.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go. Cheese.
Here we go.
Yes. Cheese.
So cute.
Here we go. Cheese.
Many of them take pictures of me.
Seafood 101
It's so good!
That's great.
Did you get a good one?
Yes, I brought the wind into the feature with the latch!
Thank you very much.
I'm a sucker for wind.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, my God.
I'll get it.
Is that the back?
Is that the front?
Which one is it?Which one?
Back?
There's something tuna-like in there.
Hey!
Is it going to take to the sky? Like a jet.
It's a front.
It's cute.
Do you think it'll light up? Maybe.
At night.
It bounces with color.
Maybe it'll have an expression.
It's still black.
It's black.
Hey! It was black.
More spots.
Let's go!
I'm sure we can find a spot.
Let's go get a drink.
Brown sugar milk.
I'm almost ready for brown sugar milk tea.
I think I like milk tea.
I don't drink much.
I like brown sugar milk better.
The sweetness is so good.
It's a nice harmony.
Maybe I can go.
Ibaraki
Kawasawa, Ibaraki
It's a touchy subject, isn't it?
Touching
It's touching!
It is touching.
Thank you very much.
This is in preparation.
That's a lot of food.
Apples, apples, apples.
It's a beautiful night when you come at night.
I definitely want to come at night.
I want to come!
It was colder than I thought it would be in Taiwan.
It was cold!
I saw the temperature was 14 or 12 degrees Celsius.
It's so cold!
Very cold!
But there are a lot of stores, so it's easy to get in.
It warms you up.
But I thought it would be warmer.
It's so wintery.
Yeah, it was winter.
It was a dream.
It was beautifully painted.
NAGOYAJU
Server
Like this in the crawlspace of
This is the server
This is a server
This is the server.
Here's the server.
Look at that.
That's a big one.
It's a server.
Oh, look at that.
This isn't Ute Aquinary.
Oh, my God.
It's a server.
It's a saga.
You can go to Saga's.
There's a particularly good one.
Oh, really.
It's the Ute Cleanery.
Amazing.
Oh, yes.
That's great.
It is.
It's like it's for an excerpt already.
This is...
It's a guideline.
OK.
Oh, there's more and more behind you.
Cute.
Grandpa's terminology.
That's my grandfather's term.
Mei-chan?
It says "Mei.
Really?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hm.
Mm-mm.
What is this place?
Matsuyama...
Cal...
Culture...
And...
Creative Park
You are here at
Here we are!
Ta-da!
I can't see a thing.
I can't see.
Creative Park
It's cute.
There's something here.
What's this?
There's a lot of bugs.
It's crazy!
I'm afraid I'm gonna fall.
Oh, my camera!
Be careful!
This is like Ohori Park in Japan.
It's amazing!
It's like...
You feel like you're in a country?
Country?
Country.
It's like we're in a different country.
The trees are different.
Yes, they are.
Foreign trees.
These are trees from overseas.
Oh, there's a river running through it.
I took the same picture.
The leaves are totally different.
They're all different.
We're crossing a bridge.
They're crossing a tiny bridge.
It's so cute.
I'm gonna get drunk... like this.
I don't know.
It's so cute.
It's so round.
There's a lot of stuff.
What's that written on it?
Isn't this where we were just now?
We just went there.
The Lantern Festival.
I see.
Not at all.
Where are we?
What's that?
I don't know where we are.
We don't know where we are.
This is where we just went, isn't it?This is where we just went, isn't it?
That's right.
This is where we went, right?
They haven't projected his face yet?
I see.
I don't understand.
I didn't understand.
I didn't know.
There aren't many stores.
Look at this.
Cute.
Stylish.
Loving.
So much love.
Hey.
Yes, but...
Yeah, but...
But you don't make it?
That's sad.
You love her, but you don't make her?
Drama.
Drama! Drama! Drama!
This season's drama. It's going to be that kind of drama.
Wow, it's so high!
It's so high up!
Is that a chimney?
It's a chimney! Maybe it's a chimney!
It's long.
Do you like coffee?
I'm a coffee drinker. I'm a graphic coffee drinker.
You can drink coffee?
Not at all.
It's amazing.
But it's not quite as good as it tastes.
I'm an adult.
You're an adult.
If they serve it to me...
I'd be like...
I'd give it to you.
I can drink a lot.
Wow, that's great.
But Keena is probably better.
Yeah, I have an image of Keena coffee.
From the top... oh, I guess that's the boyfriend's point of view.
We did it yesterday.
Oh, you did?
Heh.
You smell like Taiwan.
It's Taiwanese food.
You're right, I'm hungry.
I'm so hungry.
What do you want to eat?
Let's see...
I'll have a Hashago Romp.
I want a Hashago Romp.
You haven't eaten yet.
No, I haven't.
I want some.
I was so hungry on the first day.
It was so good.
It was delicious.
I ate it.
I put pineapple in it.
Oh, yeah...
There was also fried rice.
It's good fried rice.
It's so crispy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Real fried rice.
It's true.
I don't know what it is.
It's crazy right now.
I need a hot drink.
I want a hot drink.
You want a hot drink.
I know what you mean.
It's cold here in Taiwan.
About the same as Japan.
About the same.
I thought it might be a little warmer.
But it wasn't at all.
No, it wasn't.
It's cold.
This hair is so stylish!
Very stylish.
Not that one.
Like in Kyoto.
I want to match it with the scenery.
Of course.
You're good at taking pictures, Ai.
I'm always looking at her.
I look at them and wonder how to take them.
You take so many.
From these...
A little in front of you.
Oh, yeah?
It's so beautiful.
I can hear them singing.
I know it.
I can hear it.
A general store?
See you in the next video!
Premiere onlei
I'm ready to shop.
I was able to do it.
That was fun.
It was fun.
I bought it.
It's a cute bag.
I thought it was cute too.
They're so different every time.
Did you buy something too, Sakura?
I couldn't buy anything, I was too worried about it.
I didn't buy anything.
I bought souvenirs for Miyu, too.
I bought Miyu's souvenirs, too.
It was a lot of fun.
It was fun.
It was cold, though.
I guess so.
Let's go out for dinner next time.
Yes, let's go out to eat next time.
Let's go eat.
Let's go.